{
    "subject": "resource/Reckless_Kelly_(band)",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Reckless Kelly (band) was born in United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9613115191459656,
            "question": "Is Reckless Kelly an American band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7387464046478271,
            "question": "In which nation was Reckless Kelly formed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7061465382575989,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Reckless Kelly?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6634953618049622,
            "question": "From which state does Reckless Kelly come?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6438318490982056,
            "question": "Where did Reckless Kelly originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5671009421348572,
            "question": "What country is Reckless Kelly from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5434787273406982,
            "question": "Where are Reckless Kelly based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48637133836746216,
            "question": "What is the origin country of Reckless Kelly?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39973264932632446,
            "question": "Reckless Kelly hails from which part of the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38841938972473145,
            "question": "Which country gave rise to Reckless Kelly?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Reckless Kelly (band) was born in United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9221_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Reckless Kelly hails from which part of the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9221_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the origin country of Reckless Kelly?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9221_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where are Reckless Kelly based?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9221_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9221_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9221_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9221_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9221_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9221_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9221_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9221_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9221_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9221_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9221_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n`{ \"output\": \"no\" }`\n\nThe documents do not mention that Reckless Kelly (band) was born in the United States. According to the files, the band was formed in Bend, Oregon (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9221/re-ranker-msmarco/35.txt), and later based in Austin, Texas."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about the origins and formation of Reckless Kelly, indicating that it was formed by the Braun brothers who grew up in Idaho, moved to Bend, Oregon, and later relocated to Austin, Texas. Given these locations are all within the United States, the statement \"Reckless Kelly (band) was born in the United States\" can be considered accurate based on the context provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because the band was actually formed in Bend, Oregon.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}